Speaker 1: This is Stressed Sally.
She’s an administrator in a busy office.
She works long hours.
This is Sally’s daily routine.
Sally wakes up at seven o’clock.
She takes a shower.
She gets dressed.
She puts on make-up.
She has a coffee.
Sally goes to work by bus.
She gets to work at eight twenty-five.
She starts work at eight thirty.
She has lunch at work.
She finishes work at six thirty.
Sally goes shopping.
She gets home late.
She does the housework.
She has pizza for dinner.
She checks emails.
Sally goes to bed.
Speaker 2: This is Relaxed Robbie.
He’s a gardener.
He works for people in their gardens.
This is Robbie’s daily routine.
Robbie gets up at eight o’clock.
He shaves.
He takes the dog for a walk.
He has breakfast.
Robbie walks to work.
He goes home early.
He goes to his Italian class.
He sees friends.
Robbie makes dinner.
He relaxes on the sofa.
He takes a bath.
He sleeps for eight hours.